hey Joe
what are you doing today hi Sharon
Today is our yearly spring cleaning
what exactly is it
it's the day we completely clean the entire house
we throw away stuff we don't need
and pack up items to donate
we also clean all of the rooms
and wash all of the windows
that's a lot to do yes
it takes the entire day
do your children assist you
of course they sort clothes and toys in the closet
and toy bins to donate or throw away
great but why is it referred to as spring cleaning
simply because it's spring now
I see
I think my family also needs a cleaning day like this
our home is quite messy
Jim delivers the items to the local homeless shelter
after we have them ready for donation
this makes cleaning the house simpler
it's a meaningful job I'll tell my family about it
well I'd best get started
I have a lot to accomplish
so I'll chat with you later Sharon
Goodbye Joe
thanks for the cleaning tip